easyofficepools.com 2016-10-23

# Easy Office Pools Privacy Policy

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for easyofficepools.com.

This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

## Information Collection, Use, and Sharing

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your email address and password to grant you permissions to edit a team you’ve created for a pool or edit a pool you’ve created.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request (for example, to respond to an email question you may have about how our software works or request a password reset).  

If you are admin of a pool, your email address will be shared with anyone that adds a team to your pool.

If you’ve added a team to a pool, your name (not your email) may be visible to anyone who accesses the VIEW page for your pool. Your email and name are visible to the pool admin on their password protected ADMIN page. Pool admins will likely contact you via email.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.  

Google Analytics (GA) is used to track the following:

  * What website you came from to get here.
  * How long you stay for.
  * What kind of computer you’re using.
  * And quite a bit more.

The GA tracking information allows us to better understand the kind of people who come to our site and what actions they’re taking. This allows us to make better designs and technology.

When you get an email confirmation, password reset confirmation, or a broadcast email, a 3rd party service called Mailchimp is used. Mailchimp stores your email address but does not send emails to you that aren’t affiliated with Easy Office Pools.

When you contact us via email, a 3rd party service called Helpscout is used. Helpscout keeps a record of all emails but does not send emails to you that aren’t affiliated with Easy Office Pools.

## Your Access to and Control Over Information

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address given on our website contact page:

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

## Security

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected as follows:

  * Credit card information is not stored nor processed on our website, but instead managed via Paypal to insure transactions are processed securely. 
  * We encrypt passwords stored in our databases, except for “entrant passwords”, used by many people to gain entry to a pool, which are stored in plain text as they are intended to be shared broadly. 

## Updates

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.

**If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via the email address provided on our website contact page.**
